const list = [
  {
    qid: 1,
    question: "Where was Anjola born ?",
    context: "Anjola was born in Ogbomoso in 1981",
    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso", answer: true },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle" },
    ],
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    qid: 2,
    question: "Where was Adeola born ?",
    context: "Adeola was born in Newcastle in 1982",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Ogun",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 3,
    question: "Where was Ojo born ?",
    context: "Ojo was born in Kogi in 1902",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 4,
    question: "Where was Alagba born ?",
    context: "Alagba was born in Ijebu in 1989",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 5,
    question: "Where was Shukura born ?",
    context: "Shukura was born in Ijebu in 1989",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 6,
    question: "Where was Deji born ?",
    context: "Deji was born in Ijebu in 1989",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso", answer: true },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle" },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 7,
    question: "Where was Okele born ?",
    context: "okele was born in Ibadan in 1989",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 8,
    question: "Where was Fela born ?",
    context: "Fela was born in Kalakuta in 1989",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 9,
    question: "Where was Solo born ?",
    context: "Solo was born in KoloTown in 1900",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    qid: 10,
    question: "Where was broda Shaggi born ?",
    context: "Brother Shaggi was born in Jamaica in 1979",

    options: [
      {
        id: "a",
        choice: "Igbara",
      },
      { id: "b", choice: "Ogbomoso" },
      { id: "c", choice: "Ibadan" },
      { id: "d", choice: "Newcastle", answer: true },
    ],
    answer: "d",
  },
];

export default list;
